The next move I am going to show you is called pistol hips.
Again, you want to make sure you are in proper posture.
And, for this one, I find it a little bit easier if you sink a little bit more down into your knees.
Usually about this stance for your proper stance for this one.
Sunk down a little bit more into your knees.
What I do is let one hip go, then the other hip.
One hip, and the other hip.
And, how you get this is I drop one hip at the knee.
The knee comes out a little bit further than the other knee.
And, then the other knee.
Bring one knee out and down a little further.
Then the other knee.
Knee.
Again, the knee is dropping down and out.
Down and out.
Now, while you are doing that, when the hip comes out you want to squeeze your butt.
So, drop squeeze.
Squeeze.
This is called your pistol hips.
What you can do is you can pick up the pace.
Drop.
Make sure you are squeezing.
This is your pistol hips.